Hello traders welcome to Jari,
I am Ashish Chaturvedi with you and
hello I am Kushal Gupta with you, it is the
first day of trading yafte and the way
Nifty indicators are showing, there are
definitely signs of a huge fall in the markets,
but in this way in
effect I would say that a very good recovery from the lower levels exists,
around 80-90 points are seen coming in Nifty as well and the
Daur Daur features may be an indicator of this thing
because a rise of 64 points is
also seen in two futures, so when
we opened in the morning there was a
fall of around 200-210 points here, now you see there is a
fall of almost 128 points only,
so we will have to see how the markets react when they open,
however due to the
concern about craters in the global markets,
we got to experience a huge fall in the US markets
in Friday's session, almost
such a thing was seen coming at 3:45 and somewhere or the other
now  There are indications that we need to see
what impact this has on all the Indian banks today. But certainly, the
kind of mood that was created in Friday's session, the
momentum
looks quite strong. The momentum is strong. There has been a slight
recovery in the downturns, but
still, strangely, Nifty is showing a decline of 125 points.
Initially, there was a decline of more than 200 points.
Or Kushal. First of all, tell me, who is
buying crack in cash? You see,
I am buying in cash, the packaging film company
Cosmophi. Cosmo First. Here, the
earlier name was Cosmo Films. Now it has become Cosmo First.
Certainly, the reason for buying this here is that
they have started their specialized poppet line
and have
started it with a capacity of 30,000 tricycles per annum. So,
certainly, the kind of capacity expansion that has been done
and now the production is happening in a commercial way,
it gets a big support on their revenue in the future and
that is why the opinion is to buy Cosmo First.
862 Best Stock Plus for a target of ₹900 What have
you
bought I am buying HUDCO Here you
should focus and proceed, there is nothing much
upset but you can
see some face here
Actually if you look at it, the Maharashtra government has
issued a global tender for Dharavi Red Development, though it is
not a big deal, we have been hearing about Dharavi Red Development for
years, it has been 15-20 years since we
heard about it, nothing concrete has happened yet,
but the news has an impact, the market is
completely sentiment driven, so they
will buy here, for a target of 36
you will have to place a stop loss of ₹35 Let's move
towards futures and look at futures if you want to
sell, ICICI Lombard General
Insurance will get features here Short
positions because if any strength is shown in a weak market
then it should not be noted
and if any continuous fall is seen in a good market
then it should also not be ignored
ICICI Lombard Futures is
not participating in any bounce back of the market
but when the market falls  So, it is at the
forefront, so here you
can create short positions,
target 1138 and place a stop-loss at 1160. So, of course,
here you have to take a
short in ICICI Lombard and
from my side, you have to short the Mangal counter. Actually,
here, the way natural gas
prices are high, its negative
impact can be seen on it, but
Lali, the big focus is on Mangal. Some
news is coming that PNG,
which is the regulator of natural gas, has
asked the company to pay pipe transportation charges
and they will have to pay around Rs 330 crore in the next two months.
News is coming from such sources, some
reports are going on in the market, so you can see its negative
sentimental impact on Mangal.
So, sell here for 810.
You have to move on to the 848 set. So, the
futures category is complete, let's
move on to our next derivative category, which
is options.  I like the
Sports Kubota counter where
you have to buy. Actually,
compared to the expectations that the numbers you will bring will be relatively weak, the company has shown quite good performance
and the highest ever September sales of the
company have been recorded at 12000 units, in fact, 232
units. They are seen selling here, so
compared to last year, almost
40% growth is visible in their sales figures,
so
you have to buy its 2120 call option, its
price is 94, bought for a target of ₹110,
stock loss is 85 rupees. So the
stock which I have selected through options is also a selling option
and here Shriram Transport
Finance, here we
will sell through options. There is a buy option of 1180,
here you have to buy because
see the way Captain Open signals are being seen in the market, it is possible that
you may see a decline in selected banks and NBFCs,
you should focus here.  This
is a put option of 1180,
you will have to invest ₹49 for ₹63.
Stock Plus, here you
can see the fall. If you
move towards technology, then on Techno
Pick, I have heard of such a stock whose weekly
chart is good. Nothing will be understood on the daily
and there is a possibility of another red candle forming on the daily here.
But if after today there is a
gradual recovery in the market, then the
trend of the weekly chart will be
seen resuming again.
In IRCTC, it seems that you should
buy here. There is an opportunity.
After a good correction, the structure that has
formed here, due to this I am thinking that you can
buy and move ahead. The website of up to ₹100 is
visible very clearly here,
but do look at the weekly chart once,
then you will understand the setup. You have to place a separate stop of ₹800.
You do
not have to place it too far, you can leave by applying a stop loss.
You will buy IRCTC for around ₹680. So, let's go.
IRCTC is advised to buy in this.
From Ashish's side,
I have chosen Poonawala
Fincorp's counter in this category. However, the way the
global market is looking right now,
you might see a decline here initially,
but after that you can also buy here and
move on, but let the markets settle down,
then take a call on how
you want to buy in Poonawala Fincorp. Sir, the
reason for choosing this is definitely the four structures,
intake, but along with this, there is also news
that their subsidiary has been
upgraded by CARE Ratings, so
definitely due to that, this stock can
remain in focus here, but
you should trade in it only after looking at the kind of mood and environment, so you
have to buy in Poonawala Fincorp for a target of Rs 317.
Your stop loss should also be placed below Rs 300.
Tell me what is the skill on our next category funda. Okay,
for funda pick, from today I have been liking it.
In the real estate space, you
mentioned yourself and from my side, Godrej
Properties is where  But if you want to buy, actually
some news is coming that the government can
also expect a stamp duty cut and can
consider it, so
definitely it can be due to which it
remains in focus and along with this, more importantly, the
housing and office property market has
seen very good sales and is seen
making new highs between July to September, in
which obviously there was
also the period of Shraddha, so definitely because of this,
if you see, somewhere I feel
that Godrej Properties can
remain in big focus here, the entire real
estate should also be yours, in the next six months,
for 1440, if you want to buy in objective properties, then
Godrej Properties is
that stop where we will focus and move ahead,
fundamentally I like the stock continuously, it has
started from very low starting, poor friends, from ₹60, it has crossed 400,
all our shares have been achieved, but there is a
slight correction from there, but all card
logistics, it had hit a high of ₹450 for some time,
now I  I believe that you
can still buy here and move ahead. If you give it three months, the
stock will be
seen moving towards Rs 460. There is still a lot of steam left in the logistics space and a
lot of action is being seen. So we will
focus here and move ahead for Rs 460.
Next, for our category
entry today, the
stock that I like for investment today, I liked it before, I
still like it and will like it in the future too. That
stock is 3M India Manch Company, it is a one of a
kind company because it is the only company
which has a production capacity of more than 50 thousand. If
you look at auto ansellery,
you look at medical devices or there are many
product ranges, it is difficult to describe them. There are
50,000 products during the show,
so it should be started here.
This company should be given a place in its portfolio. If you
give it a year's time, then
you are getting stock around Rs 24,000
and today there are more possibilities that if
you get it at slightly lower levels, you can
enter there and move ahead.
Gradually, it is getting fully ready to reach its upward peak, that is, to
cross 30,000. If you
buy with investment, then
for investment, from today onwards,
you can get opportunities to buy on 3M India.
In the next one year, definitely
keep an eye on Bharti Airtel here as well. The way it has been
shown coming
from the level of around 650, you can see the bullish trend on this counter
and it is seen coming to the levels of almost 0.
Bharti Airtel
is a big opportunity for 5G and especially the enterprise
business company, now their focus is completely on
increasing here and you can see the
trajectory of increasing across the telecom space in the
future. So, for this
reason, include Bharti Airtel
in your portfolio for the long term.
Bharti Airtel has a target of ₹900. You
can see these numbers coming. Let's move on to the next
category which is based on news and here
I have chosen the stock. Invert Patil's logic
is exactly similar as  I had
told you about Goddess Properties and for the same
reason you have to buy in Ulta Patil
for the target of 352, 337 will be your
software, so for news from today, the
stock management which is efficient,
Eicher Motors, a company of your sector, but I am not able to understand
that there is a matter of global slowdown,
here no one is buying anything during Shraddha Paksha,
houses are being sold, cars are being
sold, two wheelers are being sold, what is
not selling,
everything is good but the market is weak, now I do
n't know what reaction will be seen, there
is still a decline of 130 points in the
sale of Eicher Motors, if you see that 130% is big then will the
decline of 130 points dominate or the big sale of 130% will be seen
dominating, we will have to
see day and night but Eicher Motors should
take a risk,
you can see up to ₹100 here, the
target is 3775 and you have placed a stop loss of ₹3650, a
good rise can be seen here,
so let's read our
last category  Which is my choice and
look here, I have all the three stocks, first of all I will
tell you that the first
stock to buy is done, I like it very much, I don't
know what happened, the stock does
not fall at all, it is continuously increasing,
and it is good, magnesized is being, R H I
M is its code, again and again we are
giving buy orders in it for small targets,
but every time we are sleeping ahead, good, that
big thing is visible here, there was
Orient Refractories, there was Orient Refrigerazi,
whose name became Ram, Ram Magnesi,
some people do not know its name, it is a
little difficult to find its name in the word list,
but the chart of the stock is very good,
you should also look at it once, it is
getting around 670, but the run has become
so bad that I am
not daring to give a big target, you can do it here by bringing a stop loss of ₹700 separately,
₹660, ₹10 below,
you can move ahead in the buying list, the
next stock in my list is
Reality, you should buy here  Yes,
because if
you look at a lot of news related to real estate, there is
talk of dependence, and Oberoi is no
less in that. The second news is that the
sales have been quite big so far. The third
news is that the Maharashtra government is talking about stamp duty
waiver. This is very big,
meaning it is very impactful. And
if you look at the stocks specifically, there is a Knight Frank
report as well. Correct, but
in that report it was said that the houses above 1 crore have been sold in the
western part of Mumbai for
more than 1 crore.
However,
if you look at the western part, the starting price is only 1 crore. You must be
seeing how impactful it is.
But in the news about the sector of one and a half years,
today there is one sector which you can see in every person in the
weak market, that
is Realty Auto. The kind of numbers that have come are
very impressive.
Realty is yes, so the sector will come to life,
you are seeing that it is getting cut down like this, you
can expect it and go ahead. Collection of
₹935. You can invest ₹910 on this top loss and last
stock.  I have a zidest life in this. Here
also you have to focus on pharma stocks. If
you look at it, there is some comfort now in
many such stocks.
After continuous decline, the structure formed at a good level is
indicating that now the
decline will end from here. And look at the market, it is
not doing well. MG is very volatile, so
how can a format be a counter where
you can park your money and leave.
Target of 395, stop loss of 380. And anyway, if you
look at the last week,
you will see a good buying trend on all the counters of pharma pieces.
Although there was not much rise, but there are
signs of a reversal.
Let's Mike, in which category, I have
two sell calls and one buy. The first one is
Bandhan Bank, where you have to sell and move ahead. In
fact, the entire space may remain
under pressure today. I feel that
you may see pressure today on the pair of stocks Bandhan Bank and RBL Bank. A
decline is also expected.
You should also look at the ex-Nifty also.
We are seeing a decline of 120 points. Now the decline has increased a bit.
Physics Nifty is currently seen trading with a decline of 165 points. So,
clear cut indications are that
you can see a gap down opening here, but
I feel that the decline here will continue and
you can see it coming in Bandhan Bank and Rab.
So Bandhan Bank is the first
call. After doing a micro test category,
your stop loss should be made at ₹270 higher site for a target of 260. The
second call is
RBL Bank. As I was telling you, there was
definitely a good rise here on
Friday, but
you can see an equal fall here today as well.
So RBL Bank is the second call
where you have a sell opinion and the
levels are around 110. The
first target will be around 108 or 107. It
can also be seen going towards 108 or 107. If the decline is big, then
on the higher side you have to leave a stock plus of ₹117.
Lastly  Who is Sterlite Tech
where you have to buy, actually
they have launched the first multi core fiber and cables,
so definitely they are a
giant in optical fiber and a new product has been
launched, 5GB has started,
keeping this in mind, you should buy Sterlite
Tech and the entire telecom space, which can
show good performance in the future, so you should
buy it and move ahead,
its pricing is around 165, you should target 170,
for today the stock loss is 162 rupees, so
you
should go here, but along with this, if you
look at SGX Nifty, then the decline of 30 points will be
seen deepening,
although it is a little better than when it started, it
seems a little better, you are seeing a little rate, I am
showing you SGX Nifty which is 16925, the
indication from the global market is also seen to be on the weak side, I am
thinking of top feature, you should see it once,
before you see it, let's see what kind of
activity is unfolding here, two features, the
third of the points is almost nil  There is
no meaning of the rise and if we
look at the nasdayak features, there is definitely a fall,
you can see a fall of half a percent, around 50 points, there is
no reversal there, so let's go, the
focus list of the B stocks
is ready and if you have missed any stock or
any level, then first let's quickly
see the features of Recap Cash stock
ICICI Lombard, you will get
short position, Shri Ram Transport
Finance, buy put option of ₹1200 with the fall in the market
and the technical weekly chart
looks very good to me, IRCTC has a
separate ₹800, fundamentally confidence is completely intact, the
target is ₹460 on All Karol Logistics and for investment, you have to
buy from today,
3M India, a company with more than 50 thousand products, you will get a
head of news in Eicher Motors,
here you will get a separate reality of ₹700, complete reality
packed action and you also have to buy in S Life,
my conviction is the highest in these D stocks,
futures trade
ICICI Lombard features here  We will
maintain short positions and go
for the target of 1138.
Here from my side, in the cash segment,
Cosmo Forge is the place where I have a buy
opinion. They have launched specialized opt films,
so commercial
applications. Now you can see, there can be a good rally here.
Also, Mangal should do qualifiers here.
Some news coming from PNGRP can have a
negative impact here.
Scotch has had a
great September month sale. We will
buy call options and go for it. Also, the
credit rating of Poonawala Fincorp and its subsidiary has been
upgraded. However,
in the market downturn, you should treat it with caution. In
fact, Godrej Properties Real
Estate Pack, Ashish has already told you that
in the next six months, a target of 1440 can be
seen here as well.
From an investment point of view, I like Bharti Airtel and the entire telecom
space. Here, a
target of ₹900 can also be seen in the next one year.
It is in continuous momentum. Stop
Gold Patil's numbers will remain in focus, but
Mike Just Category  You have to sell Bandhan Bank, RBL
Bank and Star Lite Tech,
again a telecom space company, you have to
buy here and my
best pick for today is Bharti Airtel, you
can go here for a target of Rs. So,
we have covered all the stocks and their levels
and the way you have seen a decline in the American markets here, we have to
see how the
Indian markets react today, so to
understand all these signals, let's
go straight to Share Bazaar Live with Anil Sir and Deepanshu,
currently Deepanshu has
joined us. Deepanshu, good morning, good
morning, Kushal, good morning, Ashish, the mood is
bad, it seemed that the series has
started well, after the bounce back on Friday, the
market went to the weekend in a good mood, but
after that, as there is global action, so many
news have come, what will be its reaction,
where do we have to keep an eye, how will today
's trading be, let's know about it
with the headlines in the stock market
[Music]